overallbeauty.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Notice » Overall Beauty

Overall Beauty/Website/Creator of [**Overall Beauty Minerals**](http://overallbeauty.com/product-category/overall-beauty-minerals-brand-mineral-makeup/ "Overall Beauty Minerals vegan friendly mineral makeup") your vegan friendly mineral makeup line.  
ATTN: Kim Snyder  
kim (@)overallbeauty.com  
5336 Blue Sapphire Ct.  
Elk Grove, CA 95758  
Toll Free/FAX number: 888-422-2694  
We have an official stance on animal testing and/or the use of animal ingredients used in our brand of mineral makeup we call Overall Beauty Minerals. Once thing we are very passion about is being able to state we are a vegan mineral makeup line. We do not believe in the testing on animals is right. There are difference ways to test without testing on animals. Overall Beauty Minerals does not use any ingredients that are by products of animals such as beeswax, carmine,lanolin, glycerin or other products created from animals.  
Thank you for reading this, now to our privacy Notice. 

At OverallBeauty.com, our relationship with our customers is very important! We are respectful about the privacy concerns of the visitors to the site. Overall Beauty also recognizes the valuable potential of technology to help people communicate with the companies whose web sites they visit, particularly through customer databases. OverallBeauty.com is committed to providing our customers with a secure web site to shop and will only collect the personal information that is necessary to process your order. Our customers should feel assured that access to this information will be limited to the except as explained below, and otherwise will never be sold or given to any other company.

Our customers should feel confident that the personal information is transmitted over secure servers. This information is necessary to properly process your order. Our systems limit access to this information only to employees who may need it to process your order. To complete a credit card transaction, the pertinent credit card information is securely forwarded to our credit card processor for authorization. OverallBeauty.com guarantees that our customers will only pay for those items, which they have actually authorized. Please read the following information to learn more about how and why we collect information and how the information is safeguarded.

**Children Under 13**  
You can look at our site, but you cannot make a purchase. You also cannot become a registered user, or use any service that asks for personal information. Our site is not designed for children. We do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13.This policy is designed to protect children. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your registration. We will send you a message if we do this. If you are under 13 and want to make a purchase, please ask a parent to place the order for you.

**What our Privacy Policy Covers**  
This Privacy Policy covers any personal information that OverallBeauty obtains from you when you use services on our site. This policy does not cover the practices of companies that OverallBeauty does not own or control, or the actions of people that OverallBeauty does not employ or manage. Our Privacy Policy may change in the future. We invite you to check back periodically to see if we have made any changes. If we make any material changes, we will post a notice on our home page. By using this site, you agree to the terms of our policy. For more information about the terms of use for this site, please visit our terms and conditions page.

**What & When Personal Information is collected**  
OverallBeauty will ask you for your information, including some personal data, if you use one of the services below:  
Note: If you decide not to provide information, you may not be able to use some of our services.  
In order to register, you need to share some personal information, such as your name and e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to visit OverallBeauty.com web pages. But you will have to register if you want to place orders or make full use of our services. If you opt-in during the Site registration process or at other times when you submit personally identifiable information to our Site, the information you provide may be used by OverallBeauty to create and deliver to you our newsletters, surveys or other communications containing product and event information, cosmetics tips or promotions.

**Anti-Diversion Policy  
**  
Product diversion is when someone who is not authorized to sell a product obtains the product illegally and sells it. Or even worse, tampers with the product and then sells it as the original. Professional hair care products are meant to be sold by Cosmetologists licensed by their State Board of Barbering and Cosmetology or licenced by the company to be able to offer their hair care line. Overallbeauty.com has been licensed to be able to offer all the haircare lines we offer.

**We realize that our customers trust us to protect their personal information. We take that task seriously. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.**  
If you do opt-in and later decide that you would no longer like to receive these communications please email OverallBeauty at overallb@OverallBeauty.com and we will be more than willing to remove you from all lists. If you have elected to provide us with your contact information, e.g., by registering at the Site or emailing us, we may provide you with service related announcements concerning the Site or contact you regarding your requests. For example, all registered users will receive a welcoming email to confirm their registration. These types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns and to provide the high level of customer service that OverallBeauty offers its customers. How OverallBeauty Protects Your Information with Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) authentication to guarantee the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet help protect your online transaction information from third party interception.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**  
Making a purchase when a customer places an order over our web site, we will ask for your payment method preference, credit card account number and expiration date, name as it appears on your credit card, “bill to” address, daytime phone number, and e-mail address. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of OverallBeauty.com. Our customers should feel confident that the personal information is transmitted over secure servers. This information is necessary to properly process your order. Our systems limit access to this information only to employees who may need it to process your order. To complete a credit card transaction, the pertinent credit card information is securely forwarded to our credit card processor for authorization. OverallBeauty.com guarantees that our customers will only pay for those items, which they have actually authorized.  
OverallBeauty.com likes to keep its customers informed about the latest merchandise, special offers, contests, promotions and upcoming store events through our online newsletter. OverallBeauty.com does not share our subscriber list or any of our subscriber’s information with outside parties. You can unsubscribe from the e-mail newsletter at any time. If you would like to unsubscribe from the newsletter, you may do so by clicking on the unsubscribe link included in each e-mail or by e-mailing us at kim@OverallBeauty.com

**A NOTE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS (ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 2003 –OPPA)**  
It is the intent of the Privacy Policy to comply with the California Act. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the act. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. This is not usually personally identifiable. If you purchase a product or service via this website (and thereby become covered by the Act), the purchase agreement you electronically sign prior to purchase allows the website to collect and archive all the personal information you provide and to transmit and/or transfer that personal information to third parties. There is no way you can modify this information and you have no right to do so. Under the terms of the purchase agreement, you have no right to view or receive any information about our database. In the event that the website, under advice of counsel, agrees to Divulge information, the requesting party must submit whatever information is demanded by the website to insure that the website is releasing information to the correct party. Other provisions of the OPPA may exempt this website from complying. While we take measures to ensure that outside parties do not have access to any information we have about you, we do not warranty that outside parties will not breach our system and thus have access to your information. (You should know that merchant service providers do not allow us access to your credit card information.) This Privacy Policy also is subject to change without notice. You are required to read it prior to using the website. By interacting with the website you agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy. By using the website or purchasing a product through this  
website, you waive the right to use state or federal court systems to address complaints and, instead, agree to use the American Arbitration Association located in a city and county specified herein.

**Who Views Your Personal Information**  
OverallBeauty may only share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, processing credit card payments, investigating fraud. They have access to information needed to perform their functions, but may not disclose your personally identifiable information for other purposes.  
**OverallBeauty does not currently or ever will sell, rent or license personal information** , that is not something we do here at OverallBeauty.com nor will we ever sell, rent, or share or otherwise give your information to a third party. We will never provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent.  
We collect some anonymous information about how you use the site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our web site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave the site. They are not connected to any personal information about you. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a web site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences or make shopping and purchasing merchandise more convenient for you.  
**Please note that at this time there are no Third Party Advertisers >** at this time there are no ads on OverallBeauty that are not run by or not own by OverallBeauty.  
If you click on ads, banners or hyperlinks, information will be collected by those advertiser representing other products that OverallBeauty.com does not own or control.  
‘Cookies’ usually will be placed on your hard drive, OverallBeauty.com does not have control over what happens with that information nor take responsibility over the accuracy or content of advertisers.  
With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.  
To protect our customers and our reputation, OverallBeauty.com is committed to providing a safe, comfortable online shopping environment. Our servers are secured and access to personal information is limited. OverallBeauty.com guarantees the safety of your information and will only charge you for purchases that are properly authorized. If you have any comments or concerns, you may either e-mail us at support@overallBeauty.com or call us toll-free at (888)422-2694, leave a message and someone will get back with you the next day.

**Update:** If we feel that a credit card may of been used that does not belong to the person who has ordered, if there is a chance that fraud has taken place, we reserve the right to cancel the order in question and refund back to the credit card holder. We also reserve the right not to take your order, and will refund the order. If there is a possible miss-matching of address to credit card holder we reserve the right not to take your order.

_We keep our packaging simple for Overall Beauty Minerals  
to off set the higher pricing for frilly jars, we passing the savings onto you the consumer.  
_

**Questions about This Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify, revise, amend, or change this Privacy Policy, Terms of Use Policy, Purchase Agreement, or any other policy by simply making and reposing the policy. By revisiting this site after reposing, you accept the new policy.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the content or practices of our website, you can contact OverallBeauty directly at: support@overallBeauty.com 

Newest Update 2/12/2014

**Due to the fact we sell skincare, as well as products for your nails etc. It is very important that you are understand this.**  
The statements for all products have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Results not typical. Individual results may vary.

**Legal Disclaimer:** The information provided on this site is intended for your general knowledge only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice or treatment for specific medical conditions. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health care provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. The information on this website is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Never disregard medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on Overallbeauty.com. Products sold on this site are for personal use and not for resale. All orders placed through this website are subject to Overallbeauty.com’s acceptance, in its sole discretion. This means that Overallbeauty.com may refuse to accept, or may cancel, any order, whether or not it has been confirmed, without liability to you or any third party.
